{
    "id": "b18541515ff4413ca40a025fc653c126",
    "title": "Irregular Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The child has …………………………. asleep.",
            "description": "Fallen is the past participle form of fall. ",
            "answers": [
                "fell",
                "felled",
                "fallen"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………. sorry for him.",
            "description": "Felt is the past participle of feel.",
            "answers": [
                "feeled",
                "felt",
                "feelled"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………….. the bottle with water.",
            "description": "Filled is the past participle of fill. ",
            "answers": [
                "filled",
                "fill",
                "filt"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ………………………… my bag?",
            "description": "Found is the past participle of find. ",
            "answers": [
                "find",
                "found",
                "founded"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This organization was ……………………………….. by war veterans.",
            "description": "Founded is the past participle form of found. ",
            "answers": [
                "found",
                "founded",
                "finded"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Birds ………………………………………. high in the sky.",
            "description": "Flew is the simple past of fly. ",
            "answers": [
                "flowed",
                "flew",
                "flown"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. the books on the table.",
            "description": "To lay is to put something down flat. ",
            "answers": [
                "Lay",
                "Lie",
                "Lain"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He has …………………………….. on the sofa all morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lay",
                "lain",
                "lied"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They ………………………….. in a hurry.",
            "description": "Left is the past participle of leave.",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "leaved",
                "leaven"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They …………………………. many objections.",
            "description": "Raised is the past participle of raise. ",
            "answers": [
                "rised",
                "rose",
                "raised"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………………….. the metal hard.",
            "description": "Struck is the past participle of strike. ",
            "answers": [
                "strike",
                "struck",
                "striked"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………….. his hair.",
            "description": "Stroked is the past simple form of stroke. ",
            "answers": [
                "stroke",
                "stroked",
                "strocked"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}